[
  {
    "question": "Queen – We Are the Champions (Pregunta 1)",
    "options": ["Marina", "Mercedes", "Carlos", "Álvaro", "Diego", "Sergio", "Alberto Gámez", "Alberto Humanes", "Rafa", "Laura", "Sole", "Jesús", "Adri"],
    "answer": "Carlos"
  },
  {
    "question": "Queen – We Are the Champions (Pregunta 2)",
    "options": ["Marina", "Mercedes", "Carlos", "Álvaro", "Diego", "Sergio", "Alberto Gámez", "Alberto Humanes", "Rafa", "Laura", "Sole", "Jesús", "Adri"],
    "answer": "Laura"
  },
  {
    "question": "Queen – We Are the Champions (Pregunta 3)",
    "options": ["Marina", "Mercedes", "Carlos", "Álvaro", "Diego", "Sergio", "Alberto Gámez", "Alberto Humanes", "Rafa", "Laura", "Sole", "Jesús", "Adri"],
    "answer": "Alberto Humanes"
  },
  {
    "question": "Queen – We Are the Champions (Pregunta 4)",
    "options": ["Marina", "Mercedes", "Carlos", "Álvaro", "Diego", "Sergio", "Alberto Gámez", "Alberto Humanes", "Rafa", "Laura", "Sole", "Jesús", "Adri"],
    "answer": "Diego"
  },
  {
    "question": "Queen – We Are the Champions (Pregunta 5)",
    "options": ["Marina", "Mercedes", "Carlos", "Álvaro", "Diego", "Sergio", "Alberto Gámez", "Alberto Humanes", "Rafa", "Laura", "Sole", "Jesús", "Adri"],
    "answer": "Sergio"
  },
  {
    "question": "Queen – We Are the Champions (Pregunta 6)",
    "options": ["Marina", "Mercedes", "Carlos", "Álvaro", "Diego", "Sergio", "Alberto Gámez", "Alberto Humanes", "Rafa", "Laura", "Sole", "Jesús", "Adri"],
    "answer": "Mercedes"
  },
  {
    "question": "Queen – We Are the Champions (Pregunta 7)",
    "options": ["Marina", "Mercedes", "Carlos", "Álvaro", "Diego", "Sergio", "Alberto Gámez", "Alberto Humanes", "Rafa", "Laura", "Sole", "Jesús", "Adri"],
    "answer": "Sole"
  },
  {
    "question": "Queen – We Are the Champions (Pregunta 8)",
    "options": ["Marina", "Mercedes", "Carlos", "Álvaro", "Diego", "Sergio", "Alberto Gámez", "Alberto Humanes", "Rafa", "Laura", "Sole", "Jesús", "Adri"],
    "answer": "Adri"
  },
  {
    "question": "Queen – We Are the Champions (Pregunta 9)",
    "options": ["Marina", "Mercedes", "Carlos", "Álvaro", "Diego", "Sergio", "Alberto Gámez", "Alberto Humanes", "Rafa", "Laura", "Sole", "Jesús", "Adri"],
    "answer": "Rafa"
  },
  {
    "question": "Queen – We Are the Champions (Pregunta 10)",
    "options": ["Marina", "Mercedes", "Carlos", "Álvaro", "Diego", "Sergio", "Alberto Gámez", "Alberto Humanes", "Rafa", "Laura", "Sole", "Jesús", "Adri"],
    "answer": "Jesús"
  },
  {
    "question": "Queen – We Are the Champions (Pregunta 11)",
    "options": ["Marina", "Mercedes", "Carlos", "Álvaro", "Diego", "Sergio", "Alberto Gámez", "Alberto Humanes", "Rafa", "Laura", "Sole", "Jesús", "Adri"],
    "answer": "Marina"
  },
  {
    "question": "Queen – We Are the Champions (Pregunta 12)",
    "options": ["Marina", "Mercedes", "Carlos", "Álvaro", "Diego", "Sergio", "Alberto Gámez", "Alberto Humanes", "Rafa", "Laura", "Sole", "Jesús", "Adri"],
    "answer": "Álvaro"
  },
  {
    "question": "Queen – We Are the Champions (Pregunta 13)",
    "options": ["Marina", "Mercedes", "Carlos", "Álvaro", "Diego", "Sergio", "Alberto Gámez", "Alberto Humanes", "Rafa", "Laura", "Sole", "Jesús", "Adri"],
    "answer": "Alberto Gámez"
  }
]
